Good morning
Good morning, good morning, good afternoon, good afternoon, good long time
Long time no see.
How are you? Are you sleeping?
Sleeping.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
What's that?
Water.
There's no water.
Do you have water? Maybe.
I'll tell you what.
I'm sure you'll get a lot of disapproving looks.
I'll have a grapefruit juice, then.
Wait, wait, wait.
Grapefruit juice.
I'm a little...
Like the debutante.
Grapefruit juice.
Okay, I'll have a Coke.
I'll have a Coke, please.
Coke and grapefruit juice.
I think.
A ping-pong machine?
Maybe a phone call.
Phone call.
This coqui.
A "koki"?
Like on Halloween?
On the phone.
Anna, can you order something on the phone?
I don't know. I don't do that.
You don't do that kind of thing?
I'm a senior.
Well, can I ask you to do something for me? For a junior.
What was that?
Coke.
Coke? Who's that?
I know this guy.
What was it again?
Coke and 100% grapefruit juice.
What?
Concentrated?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm a little scared.
What did he say?
He said, "Is it okay if it's a concentrate?
It's 100%. There's some kind of...
Oh, no.
He thought I was just a kid.
I thought he was okay.
I was scared.
Scared?
I brought Anna a souvenir to thank her for having me here today. A gift?
Oh!
What do you want?
My favorite oden.
You want some of this?
It's really good.
He said it was some kind of staple food.
Be careful.
You know, if you lick the wrong corner in the moving car,
I'll be careful.
This is healthy.
This is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy...this is healthy.
But Ana-chan, when we were thinking about who we should invite, she gave us a name, didn't she?
That's right. I was kind of the first to say it.
I'm so glad! Thank you! I did it!
I've never had a chance to work together with a Japanese artist. Not yet. I was the first to say, "I'm so happy! I'm so happy! Thank you! I'm so happy!
I don't have much of a chance to say "I'm so happy! Not yet.
It's more than how it was.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
I'm Cora.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Yay! Thank you very much.
We were in the same place to begin with, weren't we?
That's right. That's why I wanted to talk to you.
We were both working as idols.We are both idols.
You don't talk much? We don't talk about the old days of Yuru Meibo.
We don't talk at all.
You don't talk because people don't ask you? Do you say when they ask?
Not at all.
I'm fine.
They don't ask.
I've got a lot on my mind.
I have a lot of things on my mind.
I'm more concerned about her now than in the past.
I'm worried about a lot of things.
I guess I can't mention them because I have so many questions I want to ask her.
There are a lot of people who knew her as an idol
I know a lot of people who knew her when she was an idol.
I wonder if they have that picture.
I wonder if they have it.
With Miss Kanna.
Have you met Miss Kanna?
I haven't seen her in person.
I'm looking forward to meeting her... and taking pictures of this, this, and this.
I'll definitely do it, and I'm sure it'll get a lot of attention.
I'm sure it's going to be a hit.
I'm sure it's going to be a buzz, but we've been working together since 2013, right?
You joined Yurumelma in 2013?
But I think it was 2013, like four years.
That's about the same time.
Seriously, it was like one year.
That's right. Momo hasn't changed since then, though.
Right.
I know I haven't changed either.
Neither of us have changed at all anymore. We're both still in variety and stuff.
You stayed the same.
Ten years at this rate.
You can talk like that now. That's amazing.
I couldn't speak at all.
I'm on my own now.
I have to talk now.
Just a little bit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Ano, ano, ano, ano, ano.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who are you talking about?
Hello, hello, hello.
I like your teeth.
Like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Say you like my teeth.
I already freak myself out when I'm alone.
I know, I freak out when I'm all by myself.
All by yourself?
Yeah. I think it's a great thing.
It's difficult.
Do you ever think about what you should have said?
I mean, do you ever think to yourself, "I should have said it better that way"?
Do you worry about that?
No, I don't,
I just want to get better at speaking.
Even for you, are you a good speaker?
No, I'm not good. I'm good.
It's just the number of words, isn't it?
But on TV, it's not good to use too many words.
This one-line message was done so well by Chinatsu Wakatsuki that I steal it every time, but I learn from her technique.
I don't want to say powerful words in one line because the width of TV is limited.
Oh, I see.
It's like, so you're the type of person who talks wow like I do.
Anmika and others are like the opening of Star Wars.
It's like the opening of Star Wars.
In that sense, Ana-chan is good at it.
Ana-chan is good with everyone at once in her direction. And Ana-chan is good at creating an aura that you can't hear unless everyone turns to Ana-chan at once.
No, no, it's unconscious, but....
That is sense, sense.
It is more important to make people want to know than to be good at it, isn't it?
Oh, I see, that's true.
So, as someone who knows the old days, I think you're getting good enough.
That's right.
You're able to hold a conversation.
Yeah, I mean, it used to be impossible.
You know, YouTube, there are these short videos, right?
It's really the genre from the YuruMuruMono era.I really like that genre from the Yurumemono era.
I thought, "Wow, I missed it.
I miss it so much.
And then there was a comment about how the way he talks is different.
I've heard comments about how the way you speak has changed.
I thought it was probably a newcomer.
That's right.
I didn't know how to vocalize. I was in a different dimension.
I couldn't talk to other people, not even the members, for years.
I couldn't even say good morning.
So you were afraid to say anything?
I couldn't speak.
During that period, I couldn't do interviews.
I didn't know how to speak.
Now it's like that.
I'm told by the MC that I need to be heard.
I'm told to be more vocal.
If it's a radio show, I'm just fine with my normal voice.
If I try harder, it changes the tone of my voice.
That's what I was thinking at that level.
But when I look at it from the perspective of someone who has done it recently
I think that's how they see it... they see how much they love it.
When I saw it, it was like when I really came in.
It was the first time I saw it, so it was like I was really in it, and it was like I was standing next to you.
I was like that too in the beginning. You know, the kind of thing mom calls shiolingo.
Mama! How are you, Mommy?
Don't you look like her?
Like shiolingo, eitaso...
Oh, my God!
It's the same as before.
I like that guy.
They're the same kind of people.
I like you and Orion.
I'm in love with her.
I like her.
It's already done.
As Ringo in love.
The character of an idol
It's really established.
Yes, that's right. I was impressed by that,
And when we went out together,
I was impressed by that, and when we went out together, he would say, "Sio is a hurricane! And I was like, "Oh, my God, he's a hurricane!
And he was just like that.
But you don't know if he was born that way.
But I know that behind the scenes and out in the open.
She's just the way she is.
Yes.
So, there was a lot of trial and error.
There are things that I admire.
You know, you try things out and evolve. Humans...
We grow.
That's right.
We evolve.
There are things that are different from before.
I'm easily told I'm acting, or making something, or doing something.
But I'm not! I didn't use to use the Kansai dialect at all.
But when I was on TV...
I thought I could use my Kansai accent more. I thought it would be better to use the Kansai accent on TV, so I did.
But now, if I speak in standard Japanese like I do now...
It's like when you stop using the Kansai dialect, you've sealed the deal.
It's like a character change.
Oh, people will say that?
Yes, they do.
A lot.
It's a pain in the ass, isn't it?
Yes, it is. No, but it's my native language, Kansai-ben.
But now that I'm here, when I talk to my family at home, I speak in standard Japanese.
Oh, really?
That's right. So it's just a quasi-Japanese language that you speak.
So you do it normally.
On the other hand, you might be doing it more if you speak in Kansai dialect.
It's about the same.
So it depends on the viewer's point of view
It depends on the point of view of the viewer.
It's totally different.
That's what I'm trying to say.
When I look at your work, it looks like you're doing your best, and I'm doing my best.
You were doing your best.
When I look at it now, I wonder what she's talking about,And now, when I look at it, I wonder what I'm talking about,
I think, "What am I talking about?
After I thought, "That's enough," I started putting things out as they were.
I thought that was the best way to express myself.
No, you're right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought that was enough. I didn't care if I lost fans because of that.
Wow, that was really far fetched, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah. It's like the times are a little bit like Akihabara.
It started with moe,
It started from moe,
And then there was an era that started from moe and then rock,
Well, I think Vis was included in that,
Then, after that, it became more Yandere-esque,
I think Vis was part of it, but after that, it became more like a Yandere, or a negative or black part,
Let's show it! It's like, "Let's bring out the negativity and the black side!
I think that was the beginning of the trend.
It was a good start.
Did it become easier? Yes, it did.
It was tough for a long time, to be honest. It was a gateway. It was a good start. Did it get easier? It did.
It was tough for a long time. To be honest.
It was tough,
But the only thing that saved me was the fact that I was able to be myself.
By putting it out there, there was a noise coming in.
I was not a new novice, not a fan or anything like that.
But,
I was able to be myself, and that was a good thing.
The members were not so different from me, but it was the way I usually see you, Al-chan, that came out.
Oh, yes, that's right. It was like, "That's more like you! It was like that.
That's right.
Also, it made sense on stage,
I thought it was good.
Aro-chan on stage is really...,
I thought it was good because it made sense with the stage,
If you think of it as on stage when you are on stage, it's totally different,
It's totally different.
You perform as if you were born on stage and die on stage, don't you?
They really say a lot of things. So I want to know which is true and which is not.
The viewer wants to know which is true and which is false. The viewer wants to know which is true or false.
The viewer is looking for something. I wonder if I can give a message like that at that time. I think that the family formed her.
Yes.
It became very easy to understand.
I see.
The character.
That's true.
That's why it's easier to live.
Because everyone is prepared for it.
I see.
That's true.
People say, "It looks like a lot of work," or, "Isn't it tough?
People say, "You're forcing yourself to do this, aren't you?
But I'm not forcing myself at all.
Don't you feel that way? Let me see.
It looks like you're taking it easy.
I guess so.
It's not like everyone around here is worried about you.
I have to tell you something else.
If I don't tell him, he'll send it to me.
Mr. Yamasato...
He's a jerk.
I didn't mention my name.
Subscribe to our channel!